Guide to the Prometheus Research Library collection on Left Labor Caucuses TAM.192
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Unprocessed Materials
  - Progressive Workers Caucus, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Newspaper Guild Local 3, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - National Associaton of Broadcast Employees and Technicians Local 15, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Restaurant Workers, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Laborers' International Union of North American Local 261, circa 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Illinois Union of Social Service Employees, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Gulfcoast Pulpwood Associaton, circa 1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Farm Labor Organizing Committee, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees Local 12, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 144, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Hospital Workers, circa 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Welfare Employees Union (Michigan) Constitution, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Rank and File Caucus Draft Program, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - ILWU - General, circa 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - ILWU - General, circa 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - ILWU - General, circa 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - ILWU, circa 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - ILWU, circa 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - ILWU Local 10 (Bulletins), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - ILWU, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - ILWU, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - ILWU - Local 6, 1975-1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - General Letters, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Rothe/Local 600 Organizer, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Federal Workers, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - CPUSA, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - National Marine Engineers' Benefical Association and Botherhood of Marine Officers, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - NMU, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - NMU - Mariners Bulletin, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - NMU, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Presidential Elections, circa 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - CWA, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - USWA, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Sailors' Union of the Pacific, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Carpenters Union, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Transit Workers, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - May Day, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Statement by the AFL-CIO Executive Council on the Berlin Wall and Helsinki Accord, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Rank and File: General, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Militant Labor Civil Rights Committee, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Association for Union Democracy, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - UAW Independent Skilled Trades Council, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - United Front, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Deer Park Manufacturing Complex Newsletter, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - New York Rank and File: General, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Department Store Workers Union Local 1-S, 1972, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - SEIU 1199, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades: General, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - OCAWU OMOs, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - SSEU Oppositions General, circa 1966-1975 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - OCAW Official Union, circa 1973 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - UAW Local 906 - Militant Solidarity Caucus, circa 1970-1980 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - UAW, circa 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - UAW, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - UAW, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - UAW, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Washington Post Strike, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Press - General, circa 1970-1985 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Newspaper Guild, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Armthorpe Tannoy, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - UAW Militant Solidarity Caucus, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Teamster - TDU, circa 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - The Fifth Wheel: A Bay Area Rank and File Monthly, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters, circa 1970-1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - UAW, circa 1970-1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - ILWU, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NMU - ITPE News, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - IUE American Bosch Local 206, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - National Union of Mineworkers: Coal not Dole, circa 1983-1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Labor Notes Detroit Conference, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - MEBA NMU: The Marine Journal, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Canadian Labour Congress, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - CWA - Militant Action Caucus, circa 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Education: Journal of the New South Wales Teachers' Federation, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Printing and Kindred Industries Union (Australia), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - CWA - Militant Action Caucus, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Spartacist League, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Labor Black League for Social Defense, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Australia: Labor Publications, 1974-1984 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Canada: Labor Publications, circa 1975-1985 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - CUPW - General, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - IUE News, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - The Highway (UK), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - KKK vs. UAW Ad, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Partial listing of table of contents for archival boxes, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)